Walt Coburn papers, 1923-1977
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series I: Works, 1923-1977
  - Magazines, 1923-1977
    - Dime Western
      - "The Tenderfoot-Tough-Hand!," 10-29. April 1945 (Box 6)
      - "Ride the Death Watch!," 10-24. May 1945 (Box 6)
      - "Smoked-Cured!," 10-29. June 1945 (Box 6)
      - "The Boothill Badge Toter," 34-53. July 1945 (Box 6)
      - "Medicine Lodge Man-Breakers," 8-29. August 1945 (Box 6)
      - "Pardner Wanted-Dead or Alive!," 10-25. September 1945 (Box 6)
      - "Sheep Means Shootin'!," 10-32. October 1945 (Box 6)
      - "Hidden Valley Killer!," 28-94. November 1945 (Box 6)
      - "Hired to Kill!," 40-54. December 1945 (Box 6)
      - "Mail-Roder Outlaw," 10-25. January 1946 (Box 6)
      - "A New Boss for Bushwack Ranch," 10-25. February 1946 (Box 6)
      - "Red Rain at Los Gatos," 8-29. March 1946 (Box 6)
      - "Gun-Cub of Outlaw Ranch," 34-51. April 1946 (Box 6)
      - "Wet Cattle--Heading North!," 32-47. May 1946 (Box 6)
      - "Beans Bullets--and Quick Buryin'!," 12-28. June 1946 (Box 6)
      - "I.O.U. Six Bullets!," 6-20. July 1946 (Box 6)
      - "Black Lightening Strikes Twice!," 10-32. August 1946 (Box 6)
      - "Decoys of the diablito Death-Watch," 10-34. September 1946 (Box 6)
      - "Jimmy Dunn Deals the Boothill Ace!," 34-52. October 1946 (Box 6)
      - "The Toughest Freighter North of Hell!," 8-23. January 1947 (Box 6)
      - "Smoke-Cured Tenderfoot!," 30-43. February 1947 (Box 6)
      - "Blood-Money Gunslinger," 8-22. March 1947 (Box 6)
      - "Print it with Buckshot an' Let 'Em Roll!," 6-20. April 1947 (Box 6)
      - "Trail Fever!," 48-66. May 1947 (Box 6)
      - "Ramrod of the Gun-Trap Drive," 42-60. June 1947 (Box 6)
      - "They Don't Come Tougher!," 6-22. July 1947 (Box 6)
      - "Fill Your Hand or Fill a Grave!," 46-97. August 1947 (Box 6)
      - "They Ride By Night!," 6-23. September 1947 (Box 6)
      - "The Fight and Cow-Thief Crossing," 6-24. October 1947 (Box 6)
      - "Two Gun-Sons Hit Wild River!," 8-28. November 1947 (Box 6)
      - "Blood-Money Pardner," 6-22. December 1947 (Box 6)
      - "Too Damn Many Neighbors!," 6-23. January 1948 (Box 6)
      - "Line Your Sights on Sheepers!," 6-23. February 1948 (Box 6)
      - "Hell Begins at Horsehead Crossing!," 8-27. March 1948 (Box 6)
      - "Law of the Lawless," 8-29. April 1948 (Box 6)
      - "Hell with a Running Iron!," 36-53. July 1948 (Box 6)
      - "Cold Deck Gun-Angel," 8-31. August 1948 (Box 6)
      - "Shoot or Git Shot!," 6-27. September 1948 (Box 6)
      - "Smoky River Deadline," 8-25. November 1948 (Box 6)
      - "Wanted!," 36-60. February 1949 (Box 6)
      - "When the Gun-Devil Laughed," 8-23. May 1949 (Box 6)
      - "The Border-Busters," 34-52. August 1949 (Box 6)
      - "Dally Man--Dead Man!," 10-26. October 1949 (Box 6)
      - "Hell-In-The-Chutes!," 46-60. April 1950 (Box 6)
      - "Son of the Red Wall," 10-32. August 1950 (Box 6)
      - "Hired Gun!," 10-36. September 1950 (Box 6)
      - "Killing License," 92-104. May 1952 (Box 6)
    - Far West
      - "Chico". 1931 (Box 7)
      - "The Branding of Tenderfoot," xii/6: 1-36. July 1931 (Box 7)
      - "The Black Trail," xiii/1: 1-31. August 1931 (Box 7)
      - "Ride and Tie," xiii/2: 1-37. September 1931 (Box 7)
    - Fifteen Western Tales
      - "Brand of the Lost," 10-26. October 1948 (Box 7)
    - Fight Stories
      - "Saved by the Gong," 103-112. February 1929 (Box 7)
    - 44 Western Magazine
      - "Bull's-Eye on his Back!," 10-24. No Date (Box 7)
    - Frontier Stories
      - "Bounty," 69-83. June 1929 (Box 7)
      - "Barb Wire," xi/10: 30-57. February 1931 (Box 7)
      - "Barb Wire, part II," xi/11:41-66. March 1931 (Box 7)
      - "Barb Wire, part III," xi/12: 62-83. April 1931 (Box 7)
      - "Barb Wire, part IV," xxi/1: 68-85. May 1931 (Box 7)
      - "Barb Wire, conclusion," xii/2: 46-67. June 1931 (Box 7)
      - "Holster Harmony," xiii/2: 46-67. November-December 1932 (Box 7)
      - "Sons of the Alamo," 13/10: 96-125. Fall 1937 (Box 7)
      - "Captain Gringo," 14/8: 99-123. Fall 1940 (Box 7)
      - "Firebrand," 14/9: 92-125. Winter 1940 (Box 7)
    - Frontier Times
      - "The Blizzard," 32/1: 14-16. 1957-1958 (Box 7)
      - "Ruckus over a Fried Bobcat Dinner," 48/6: 8-12. November 1974 (Box 7)
      - "Carry Nation Soaks a Montana Cowtown," 8-12. 1975 (Box 7)
      - "New Year's Resolution," 49/3: 3. May 1975 (Box 7)
    - Giant Western
      - "Sorry Sid's Ketch Dog," 48-65. 1949 (Box 7)
      - "Hanged Man's Rep." 76-92. 1950 (Box 7)
      - "Last of the Long S," 110-131. 1950 (Box 7)
      - "The Circuit Rider's Son," 106-122. October 1951 (Box 7)
      - "Fear Branded," 108-127. 1951 (Box 7)
    - The Lariat
      - "Riders of the Purple," I/8: 1-21. August 1925 (Box 8)
      - "Cartridges Free," II/10: 1-41. October 1926 (Box 8)
      - "The Glory Hunter," 1-9. April 1926 (Box 8)
      - "The Yavapi Kid." January 1927 (Box 8)
      - "The Wild Bunch," 1-14. February 1927 (Box 8)
      - "Breed of the Brave," 1-17. September 1927 (Box 8)
      - "Hard and Fast," 1-11. October 1927 (Box 8)
      - "The Bronc Stomper," 1-12. November 1927 (Box 8)
      - "The Texas Twins," 1-10. December 1927 (Box 8)
      - "The White Lily," 1-13. January 1928 (Box 8)
      - "The Brave Maker," 1-14. February 1928 (Box 8)
      - "Branding Irons," 1-10. March 1928 (Box 8)
      - "Last of the Wild Bunch," IV/10: 3-16. October 1928 (Box 8)
      - "The Man from Peace River," IV/12: 3-10. December 1928 (Box 8)
      - "Cow Country Creed," V/1: 3-23. January 1929 (Box 8)
      - "Bull Ridin' Kid," V/6: 3-14. June 1929 (Box 8)
      - "Dude Wranglers," 49-105. December 1929 (Box 8)
      - "Lead Poisonin'," VI/4: 3-16. April 1930 (Box 8)
      - "The Black Maverick," VII: 3-15. April 1931 (Box 8)
      - "Cows Don't Have Wings!" 55-66. May 1931 (Box 8)
      - "Hog-Leg Law," 41-58. April 1932 (Box 8)
      - "Dynamite," 64-74. June 1932 (Box 8)
      - "Red Rio," 30-76. December 1932 (Box 8)
      - "The 7 Up War," 44-69. November-December 1933 (Box 8)
      - "Montana Man," 67-77. March-April 1934 (Box 8)
      - "Lone Wolf," 70-85. May-April 1934 (Box 8)
      - "Snake Sign," 80-86. August 1934 (Box 8)
      - "Limb of the Law," 107-123. October 1934 (Box 8)
      - "Bear Paw," 103-120. December 1934 (Box 8)
      - "Three Mules to Skin," 23-70. February 1935 (Box 8)
      - "Breed of the West," 29-48. April 1935 (Box 8)
      - "The Zebra Dun," 73-76. August 1935 (Box 8)
      - "Lobo of the Wastelands," 99-119. October 1935 (Box 8)
      - "He Heard the Owl Hoot," 82-122. February 1936 (Box 8)
      - "Crimson Crosses," 18-48. April 1936 (Box 8)
      - "The Ranch of the Four Winds," 34-69. June 1936 (Box 8)
      - "Riders of Fortune," 24-60. August 1936 (Box 8)
      - "Cowboy Cole--Manhunter," 86-119. October 1936 (Box 8)
      - "Doom Guns," 84-114. December 1936 (Box 8)
      - "Hell-Taming Hombre," 15-25. January 1937 (Box 8)
      - "Death Rides the Mesa," 16-23. February 1937 (Box 8)
      - "Rusty Sixes," 80-87. May 1937 (Box 8)
      - "Double-Cross Roundup," 96-122. July 1937 (Box 8)
      - "Senorita Satan," 26-33. September 1937 (Box 8)
      - "The Bullet Brander," 62-87. November 1937 (Box 8)
      - "Six-Gun Ball," 100-118. January 1938 (Box 8)
      - "Smoke Over the Range," 86-118. August 1938 (Box 8)
      - "Buscodera Blaster," 44-77. May 1938 (Box 8)
      - "The Last Lobo," 36-72. July 1938 (Box 8)
      - "Hell-Cat of the Bitter-River Range," 42-76. September 1938 (Box 8)
      - "Snake-Tracks," 90-122. January 1939 (Box 8)
      - "Black Horseman of the Badlands," 92-128. May 1939 (Box 8)
      - "Montana Hellion," 84-98. August 1939 (Box 8)
      - "Saddle and Guns to Kingdom Come," 108-128. November 1939 (Box 8)
      - "The Gun Hombre of Hell-and-Back," 90-127. January 1940 (Box 8)
      - "Senor Bardcase," 96-127. March 1940 (Box 8)
      - "Smoke-Born," 91-127. May 1940 (Box 8)
      - "The Valley of the Branded Men," 2-51. July 1940 (Box 8)
      - "The Six-Gun Traveler," 94-123. November 1940 (Box 8)
      - "Gunman Born," 94-127. January 1941 (Box 8)
      - "Rawhide Hellion," 89-123. March 1941 (Box 8)
      - "The Buckshot Legion," 104-127. May 1941 (Box 8)
      - "Fugitives of the Smoke-Trail," 94-128. July 1941 (Box 8)
      - "The Waif of Hang-Tree Range," 84-127. September 1941 (Box 8)
      - "Saga of the Singing Gunman," 64-76. November 1941 (Box 8)
      - "Moon-Trail Maverick," 4-74. January 1942 (Box 8)
      - "Payoff in Mex," 86-126. March 1942 (Box 8)
      - "Pronto Guns," 50-69. May 1942 (Box 8)
      - "Senor Sidewinder," 40-49. July 1942 (Box 8)
      - "Loco Guns," 52-66. November 1942 (Box 8)
      - "Death Slings a Sudden Gun," 92-127. January 1943 (Box 8)
      - "Queen of the Border Riders," 98-127. March 1943 (Box 8)
      - "The Ringtaled Rannyhans," 45-127. May 1943 (Box 8)
      - "Crossfire Colts," 30-48. July 1943 (Box 8)
    - Maverick Magazine
      - "Word Wrangler of the Old West," 1/8: 36-37. November 1949 (Box 9)
      - "Men of the Dark Trails," 12-41. August 1934 (Box 9)
      - "Butch Cassidy - Sheriff Maker," 74-91. September 1934 (Box 9)
      - "The Wild Bunch," 78-94. October 1934 (Box 9)
      - "Law Meets," 80-95. November 1934 (Box 8)
      - "Wild Bunch Orphan," 84-99. December 1934 (Box 9)
    - NEA Service
      - "Little Doc." July 1950 (Box 9)
    - New Western
      - "Red Killer of Grizzly Gulch," 8-28. March 1946 (Box 9)
      - "Killers' Quarantine!" 12-35. June 1946 (Box 9)
      - "Five Men for the Hanging-Bee!" 8-28. October 1946 (Box 9)
      - "Manhunt," 8-28. January 1947 (Box 9)
      - "The Bank-Bustin' Buckaroo!" 10-29. May 1947 (Box 9)
      - "Pardner Wanted-Bring Own Coffin!" 6-21. August 1947 (Box 9)
      - "Double Tough!" 6-23. September 1947 (Box 9)
      - "Blast That Gun-Ghost Down!" 6-26. October 1947 (Box 9)
      - "The Trail Herd Buccaneers," 8-32. March 1948 (Box 9)
      - "The Saga of Horse Thief Sam," 8-30. April 1948 (Box 9)
      - "Fightin' Wages-Blood an' Bullets!" 8-29. January 1949 (Box 9)
      - "Smoke Those Sooners Down!" 10-27. December 1949 (Box 9)
      - "Bring 'Em Back Dead!" 10-30. August 1950 (Box 9)
    - NorthWest Stories
      - "Bell-Metal Spurs," 2/2: 7-27. June 1925 (Box 9)
      - "Superstition House," 1-15. July 1925 (Box 9)
      - "While the Bannock Cools," 4/3: 24-34. July 1926 (Box 9)
      - "Bounty Money," 1-15. January 8, 1927 (Box 9)
      - "The Soul of Cibicu Jacks," 40-55. Augst 1927 (Box 9)
      - "Woman-Savvy," 39-46. October 1927 (Box 9)
      - "Water and Gold," 33-37. November 1927 (Box 9)
      - "Trails to Paradise," 62-69. May 1928 (Box 9)
      - "Playin' His String Out," 52-63. July 1928 (Box 9)
      - "Fightin' Wages," 66-84. June 1930 (Box 9)
      - "Poker Face," 52-59. January 1931 (Box 9)
    - Old West
      - "Till the Law Cut Us Down!" 4-7. Summer 1976 (Box 9)
    - Pioneer Western
      - "When Justice Rode by Night," 1/1: 68-96. August 1937 (Box 9)
    - Popular Western
      - "The Brand Artist," 9-27. October 1949 (Box 9)
      - "The Fletcher Kid," 11-25. June 1950 (Box 9)
      - "When Crooked Trails Cross," XXXIX/3: 9-30. December 1950 (Box 9)
    - The Quarter Horse Journal
      - "Cow Horse up North," 26-70. April 1951 (Box 9)
      - "Cow Horses of the Southwest," 9-35. August 1951 (Box 9)
      - "Ketch-Colt for Christmas," 4-27. December 1951 (Box 9)
      - "The Goober Kid," 6-22. December 1952 (Box 9)
    - Short Stories
      - "Snow Shackles," 62-70. February 1929 (Box 9)
      - "Pock-Mark," 47-63. July 1930 (Box 9)
      - "No Man's Jackpot," 25-45. August 25, 1937 (Box 9)
      - "The Trail to Hell and Back," 144-160. May 25, 1941 (Box 9)
      - "Gunsmoke at the House on Stilts," 84-113. February 1942 (Box 9)
      - "Salute to High Adventure," 6-36. June 10, 1942 (Box 9)
      - "Laying Ghosts at Burnt Ranch," 128-155. November 25, 1942 (Box 9)
      - "Blocking of Buzzard Pass," 8-32. May 25, 1943 (Box 9)
      - "Bench Warrants for the Wind River Gang," 6-30. June 25, 1943 (Box 9)
      - "Tenderfoot Tough Hand," 106-124. June 10, 1944 (Box 9)
      - "Assiniboine At Bataan," 46-56. July 25, 1944 (Box 9)
      - "Emptied guns," 48-65. February 25, 1945 (Box 9)
      - "Gringo Stand-Off," 52-68. May 25, 1945 (Box 9)
      - "Guns in San Marcos Pass," 50-67. March 10, 1946 (Box 9)
      - "The Four T Rep," 44-70. August 10, 1946 (Box 9)
      - "The Horse Thief Trap," 34-53. August 25, 1947 (Box 9)
      - "A Gun Debt Gathers Interest," 104-130. November 10, 1947 (Box 9)
      - "The Wolfer's Whelp," 118-139. June 10, 1948 (Box 9)
      - "Squawman's Island," 82-103. September 25, 1948 (Box 9)
      - "Dead Man's Trail Herd," 38-57. January 25, 1949 (Box 9)
      - "A Ticket to Chinook, Montana," 28-50. May 1949 (Box 9)
    - Star Western
      - "Nester Luck," 39-51. October 1933 (Box 10)
      - "Lone Hand," 910-115. May 1934 (Box 10)
      - "Bronc Buster's Luck," 44-51. June 1934 (Box 10)
      - "Injun List," 41-45. July 1934 (Box 10)
      - "Longrider Reckoning," 70-85. August 1934 (Box 10)
      - "Tomorrow We Die," 45-51. September 1934 (Box 10)
      - "Death Along the Rio," 43-51. November 1934 (Box 10)
      - "The Buzzard's Shadow," 88-104. January 1935 (Box 10)
      - "Renegade Retribution," 60-77. March 1935 (Box 10)
      - "Gallows Bound," 46-62. May 1935 (Box 10)
      - "The Rider From Boothill," 50-66. September 1935 (Box 10)
      - "Brand of Dishonor," 88-106. October 1935 (Box 10)
      - "Death's Saddlemates," 88-100. December 1935 (Box 10)
      - "Blood on his Badge," 54-69. May 1936 (Box 10)
      - "From Texas to Hell," 54-73. July 1936 (Box 10)
      - "the gunman God Forgot," 50-67. August 1936 (Box 10)
      - "Phantom of Lobo Valley," 50-72. September 1936 (Box 10)
      - "Brand of the Blind Gunman," 56-74. October 1936 (Box 10)
      - "The Murder Bronc Pays Off," 52-69. December 1936 (Box 10)
      - "Outlaw Bronc Rider," 52-72. January 1937 (Box 10)
      - "Tinhorns Can't Cheat Death," 70-87. February 1937 (Box 10)
      - "Tinhorn Outlaw," 54-67. March 1937 (Box 10)
      - "The Kid Who Tamed the Badlands," 56-75. June 1937 (Box 10)
      - "Law of the Thundering Herds," 56-73. December 1937 (Box 10)
      - "Partners Through Hell and Glory," 8-39. February 1938 (Box 10)
      - "Last Stand of the Freeze-Out Pool," 10-40. March 1938 (Box 10)
      - "Gun-Chore for a Texan," 48-65. April 1938 (Box 10)
      - "Partners Into Purgatory," 8-35. June 1938 (Box 10)
      - "Death Rides the Drag R," 11-36. April 1939 (Box 10)
      - "Gunsmoke Cures a Wheel-Chair Cowman," 9-39. May 1939 (Box 10)
      - "The Block K Rides Tonight!" 7-35. July 1939 (Box 10)
      - "Texas Guns Head North," 6-27. September 1939 (Box 10)
      - "Hell Starts at Gringo Doyles," 6-29. October 1939 (Box 10)
      - "Blood Buys A Dead Man's Cavvy," 8-35. January 1940 (Box 10)
      - "Broc-Buster Wanted--Dead or Alive!" 8-31. March 1941 (Box 10)
      - "Bullet-Heir to Cottonwood Valley," 10-37. June 1941 (Box 10)
      - "Hell's Pitchfork Army," 11-41. November 1941 (Box 10)
      - "Gun-Cub Law," 11-36. January 1942 (Box 10)
      - "Death Buys a Trail Herd," 10-35. April 1942 (Box 10)
      - "Death Follows the Mad Wolfer," 10-32. September 1942 (Box 10)
      - "Tougher Than A Boot!" 10-41. October 1942 (Box 10)
      - "Ghost of the Frontier Battalion," 38-55. December 1942 (Box 10)
      - "The Killer of Rustlers' Roost," 76-95. January 1943 (Box 10)
      - "Gunsmoke Makes a Man!" 12-42. February 1943 (Box 10)
      - "Outcast of Murder Ranch," 10-33. March 1943 (Box 10)
      - "Missouri River Gun Tally," 9-27. April 1943 (Box 10)
      - "The Line Camp Terror," 8-25. May 1943 (Box 10)
      - "Pardners of Massacre Ranch," 8-25. June 1943 (Box 10)
      - "Manhunt!" 56-69. July 1943 (Box 10)
      - "One More Bronc To Ride," 8-25. August 1943 (Box 10)
      - "Hell's Home Ranch," 8-25. September 1943 (Box 10)
      - "Gun-Courage!" 10-27. October 1943 (Box 10)
      - "Rodeo Renegades," 8-23. November 1943 (Box 10)
      - "The Son of Horse Thief Britt," 8-25. December 1943 (Box 10)
      - "Cotton Top Gets Tough!" 9-23. January 1944 (Box 10)
      - "Tenderfoot Jones," 8-25. February 1944 (Box 10)
      - "Coffins for Fence-Cutters!" 8-18. March 1944 (Box 10)
      - "Texas Guns Not for Hire," 8-21. May 1944 (Box 10)
      - "The Hunting of Long Fack Maverty," 8-22. June 1944 (Box 10)
      - "The Locoed Kid's Private War," 48-61. July 1944 (Box 10)
      - "The 77's Brand-Blot Army," 8-21. August 1944 (Box 10)
      - "The Busting of Bear Paw Pool," 11-21. September 1944 (Box 10)
      - "The Moccasin Track Invasion," 42-53. October 1944 (Box 10)
      - "Hot-Lead Mortgage--Past Due!" 10-22. November 1944 (Box 10)
      - "Coffin-Branded!" 38-47. December 1944 (Box 10)
      - "The Gunsmoke Grubstaker," 10-37. January 1945 (Box 10)
      - "Bring 'Em Back Dead!" 8-17. February 1945 (Box 10)
      - "The Running-Iron Rebels," 10-23. March 1945 (Box 10)
      - "The Man-Trap Ranch." April 1945 (Box 10)
      - "The Saga of Curly Ben," 11-24. May 1945 (Box 10)
      - "Cabin-Fever!" 10-22. June 1945 (Box 10)
      - "Ride Wide of Buzzard Well!" 42-62. July 1945 (Box 10)
      - "Rocky Point's Bullet Convention," 8-22. August 1945 (Box 10)
      - "For the Bulls of Jajaral," 10-27. September 1945 (Box 10)
      - "Badland Gun-Busters!" 40-55. October 1945 (Box 10)
      - "The Gunman Who Rode Alone," 10-24. November 1945 (Box 10)
      - "Cold-Decked!" 10-25. December 1945 (Box 10)
      - "Your Badge is a Target!" 10-21. January 1946 (Box 10)
      - "Through the Smoke!" 10-26. February 1946 (Box 10)
      - "Here's Lead in Your Eye!" 46-60. March 1946 (Box 10)
      - "The Ranch that Death Built," 37-53. April 1946 (Box 10)
      - "Black Dice," 8-30. May 1946 (Box 10)
      - "Tally his Ears!" 12-26. June 1946 (Box 10)
      - "When Pardners Pack Guns!" 48-62. July 1946 (Box 10)
      - "The Gun-Prayer of Leaning-T Lubbock," 10-32. September 1946 (Box 10)
      - "The Coyote Kid-Fighting Man!" 44-59. October 1946 (Box 10)
      - "Across the Deadline Into Hell!" 10-27. November 1946 (Box 10)
      - "Joker Law for Coulee County!" 10-29. December 1946 (Box 10)
      - "Then Satan Sent the Sodbuster!" 8-22. January 1947 (Box 10)
      - "Boot-Tough Ain't Bullet Proof!" 6-19. April 1947 (Box 10)
      - "Deer Lodge Fighting Man," 10-31. May 1947 (Box 10)
      - "Free-Range--If You Fight for It!" 6-27. July 1947 (Box 10)
      - "Senor Cow Thief Runs for Sheriff!" 6-22. August 1947 (Box 10)
      - "Ride Clear of CatClaw!" 50-71. September 1947 (Box 10)
      - "The Devil Sent His Gun-Angels!" 6-23. October 1947 (Box 10)
      - "Ride Home to the Hang-Tree!" 6-21. December 1947 (Box 10)
      - "Wet Cattle in Gringo Pass!" 6-25. January 1948 (Box 10)
      - "The Devil's Orphan," 8-32. March 1948 (Box 10)
      - "Gun-Cub's Hellcat--Keep Off!" 10-28. October 1948 (Box 10)
      - "The Border-Hopper Gets Tough!" 10-26. August 1949 (Box 10)
    - 10 Story Western
      - "Devil's Playground," 44-62. August 1936 (Box 11)
      - "Doc Bean - Badlands Medico," 44-61. September 1936 (Box 11)
      - "Son of the Wild Bunch," 10-34. October 1936 (Box 11)
      - "Fighting Pay at the Quien Sabe," 10-34. November 1936 (Box 11)
      - "A Tenderfoot Rides to War!" 8-34. January 1937 (Box 11)
      - "Gun Ghost of the Muleshow Mine," 10-37. March 1937 (Box 11)
      - Snowed In--With Death!" 56-74. April 1937 (Box 11)
      - "Ghost Rider From Powder River," 10-38. May 1937 (Box 11)
      - "Death Drives Shotgun Grade," 50-68. June 1937 (Box 11)
      - "Rebellion at Rustler's Crossing," 50-69. July 1937 (Box 11)
      - "Fighting Wages at Coffin Ranch," 8-37. August 1937 (Box 11)
      - "Dead Heros Guard the Stage," 52-72. September 1937 (Box 11)
      - "Misswouri River Gun Castaways," 10-40. October 1937 (Box 11)
      - "The Button Buys a War," 8-28. November 1937 (Box 11)
      - "Satan's Saddlemate," 33-39. April 1944 (Box 11)
      - "Payoff at Poverty Flat," 36-43. May 1944 (Box 11)
      - "Phantom Scourge of Skull Valley," 10-24. December 1944 (Box 11)
      - "Tinhorn King of Haunted Range," 8-26. February 1945 (Box 11)
      - "Here's Blood in Your Eye!" 8-27. August 1945 (Box 11)
      - "Hell for Sale!" 10-29. January 1946 (Box 11)
      - "That Milk River Fightin' Clan!" 8-25. May 1946 (Box 11)
      - "Boss of Ghost Herd," 10-26. September 1946 (Box 11)
      - "That Texican Tornado Man!" 8-24. January 1947 (Box 11)
      - "Scourge of the Craven Clan," 6-17. July 1947 (Box 11)
      - "Powdersmoke Puppet," 6-20. December 1947 (Box 11)
      - "Renegade Keeper of the Border Bastion," 8-25. March 1948 (Box 11)
      - "Gun Music Spooks the Lazy S," 10-21. October 1948 (Box 11)
      - "Lightnin' Brands a Cattle King," 14-27. December 1947 (Box 11)
      - "Wolf Man of the Crimson Ice," 8-24. May 1949 (Box 11)
      - "Death Ramrods of the Triangle B," 8-25. March 1949 (Box 11)
      - "Glory Hunter," 52-125. May 1950 (Box 11)
      - "Blood Trial in the Yellow Hills," 70-86. September 1950 (Box 11)
      - "Satan Rods this Roundup!" 14-28. August 1951 (Box 11)
      - "I Wear My Father's Guns," 10-112. December 1951 (Box 11)
    - Tops in Western Stories
      - "Crossfire Colts," 1-32. Fall 1953 (Box 11)
    - Triple X
      - "The Poddie," 16-36. March 1927 (Box 11)
      - "Twisting the Devil's Tail," 16-33. May 1927 (Box 11)
    - Triple Western
      - "When Crooked Trails Cross," 80-99. Fall (Box 11)
    - True West
      - "No Re-Ride," 2/1: 11-12. August-September 1954 (Box 11)
      - "The Honor of Old Thunder," 2/2: 16-17. October-November 1954 (Box 11)
      - "Last Hanging in Arizona," 5/5: 16-17. May-June 1958 (Box 11)
      - "Loops and Swift Horses Are Surer Than Lead," 14/4: 22-24. April 1967 (Box 11)
      - "My Thirty Years as a Pulp Writer," 6-9. 1967 (Box 11)
      - "King of the Westerns," 14/6: 3-68. August 1967 (Box 11)
      - "The Injuns Called Him Medicine Man," 16/3: 6-9. January-February 1969 (Box 11)
      - "Navajo Traders for Many Moons," 16/4: 6-9. April 1969 (Box 11)
      - "My Friend, Guy Weadick," 20/6: 14-18. July-August 1973 (Box 11)
      - "The Big Un," 21/4: 6-8. March-April 1974 (Box 11)
      - "Summer of the Blue Snow," 21/8: 14-15. July-August 1974 (Box 11)
      - "Uncle Billy Jacobs' Story," 24/6: 8-11. July-August 1977 (Box 11)
    - West
      - "The Pot Hook Trail," XXXIV/1: 6-33. June 22, 1932 (Box 11)
      - "Stampede," XXXIV/4: 6-48. August 3, 1932 (Box 11)
      - "Water Rights," XXXV/3: 47-66. November 1932 (Box 11)
      - "Pud Ackley, Cowboy," 6-22. December 1933 (Box 11)
      - "Cowboys I Have Known," by Guy Weadick, story About Walt Coburn, 40-45. May 1936 (Box 11)
    - Walt Coburn's Action Novels
      - "The Four Aces." 1931 (Box 12)
      - "Cartridges Free." 1931 (Box 12)
      - "Paths to Glory." 1931 (Box 12)
      - "The Maverick Legion." 1931 (Box 12)
    - Walt Coburn's Western Magazine
      - "Brother of the Gun," 1/2: 10-44. December 1949 (Box 12)
      - "Walt Coburn's Home Corral," 1/2: 8-9. December 1949 (Box 12)
      - "The Raw Red Trail to Dodge," 1/1: 10-44. November 1949 (Box 12)
      - "Walt Coburn's Home Corral," 1/1: 6-9. November 1949 (Box 12)
      - "Buckshot Blue's Partner," 1/3: 8-43. January 1950 (Box 12)
      - "Walt Coburn's Home Corral," 1/3: 6-7. January 1950 (Box 12)
      - "The Hoot-Owl Syndicate," 1/4: 8-37. February 1950 (Box 12)
      - "Walt's Tally Book," 1/4: 6-7. February 1950 (Box 12)
      - "The Fighting Tinhorn," 2/1: 10-36. March 1950 (Box 12)
      - "Walt's Tally Book," 2/1: 78-79. March 1950 (Box 12)
      - "Load Your Guns - Dig Your Graves!" 2/2: 10-40. April 1950 (Box 12)
      - "Walt's Tally Book," 2/2: 6-9. April 1950 (Box 12)